Excuse me, ma'am. Ma'am, question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
28 years old? And then how did you get rich?
Um, you're not going to ask
me when I became a billionaire.
Are you serious? How did you
get rich? How'd you become a billionaire?
I have more than 10 companies around the world.
And what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
I created one of the
greatest fitness products on the planet.
So you're a business owner?
More than a business owner. I
also master the art of communication.
I've sold over two and a
half billion dollars worth of products.
Are you playing bad real quick?
I play defensive end for the Cleveland Browns.
You're one of the greatest defensive ends of all time.
I mean, if you say so.
Did you come from a lot of money?
Absolutely not. Flat-out broke.
But I'm going to tell you something.
I also raised a little boy from South Central.
I had him for 12 years
of my life, and he was murdered.
People hit rock bottom all the time.
Most of them stay there, get comfortable,
build a couch and a house down there.
Don't do that.
The best thing in life you can do
is go down and spring right back up.
How old were you when you became a billionaire?
I'm a bus.
Seven, eight years ago.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
I often say, when kids are growing up, we've
been taught to talk about sex and not money.
But the analogy is, the
answer is, money's much more important.
I'm going to challenge you right now.
Take me back to the most life-changing conversation
you ever had.
What's the greatest piece of advice
that you've received throughout your career?
This is Beverly Hills, one of the most
expensive and powerful zip codes in the world.
This small stretch of Los Angeles has quietly become
one of the most concentrated hubs of wealth in America.
So today, I'm going to be walking up
to some of the wealthiest and most influential people
in Los Angeles and asking them
how they actually made their money.
From a woman billionaire who
owns companies all over the world,
to one of the highest paid and most dominant,
NFL players of all time, Miles Garrett.
And later on in this video, I'm going
to be going inside a private red carpet event,
interviewing one of the richest men in Los Angeles.
This is someone who's worth
billions and almost never does interviews.
Look, by the end of this video,
you'll see how people at completely different levels
built their wealth and what it actually
takes to become financially free in today's world.
So this video is about to
be insane from start to finish.
Stay tuned.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
So, let's get this video started.
Let's go.
So, I'm here in Los Angeles, California.
I'm with the
President of the United States,
and I'm here with my friend,
my friend,
my friend.
My friend,
My friend, my friend.
Oh, this guy.
Yeah.
How did I get rich?
There's some guys here, Laura,
asking me how I got rich.
I'm not rich.
Sir, so I grew to another 20 million followers.
I've interviewed Tom Cruise, Dana White, Tom Brady.
What line of business were you in?
What did you do?
I'll get back to you.
Listen, I got to finish this call.
I'll come back and find you.
Guys, look.
As you can see, man, everybody in
Los Angeles is always on their damn phone.
I mean, it's impossible to get
these people to stop and talk, man.
But look, we came all the way out to Los
Angeles, so I'm not going to stop until I run into
some of the billionaires that live and work
out here and build their empires, you guys.
So hang tight.
Let's go find the millionaires
and billionaires that run Los Angeles.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am, question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
28 years old?
And then how did you get rich?
You're not going to ask
me when I became a billionaire.
Are you serious?
How did you get rich?
What did you do?
How did you become a billionaire?
I have more than 10 companies around the world.
And what was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
When I was young, $80 million in six months.
$80 million in six months?
Could I interview you for a minute?
I interview billionaires all over the
world to help the younger generation.
Is that cool?
Okay, that's cool.
Did you come from Los Angeles?
Did you make a lot of money?
Did you start out with a lot of money?
I started with negative debt of $3 million.
How?
My family member passed away and I
inherited $3 million in debt, not in cash.
You made $80 million in six months.
What is the best financial advice
you would give to the younger generation?
Ignorance is expensive.
So learn to swim before you drown.
Did you have people that doubted you in business?
Oh, of course.
That's one thing.
The most important lesson I would
give to anyone, save your energy.
Don't ever try to make
people understand you or get approved.
You only need to please God.
Because humans, you can never please them.
They can't even please themselves.
If you keep trying to please humans,
you will waste a lot of energy.
The moment you stop making people think you're
good, that moment, your life takes a leap.
Did you go to university?
Yes, of course.
I had two master's degrees before I was
20 years old, one postgraduate degree since I
was 19, and a PhD.
Did college help you become a billionaire or no?
Of course, because college gives me discipline.
I love that.
I love learning.
I don't stop learning.
I'm going to take a few more
master's degrees and a few more PhDs.
What's one lesson about business that you would
teach me right here that is not taught
in business school?
A lot of people aim for sales,
for revenue, for the figure of the revenue.
No, not the revenue, not even profit.
Because your profit could be hidden in
the bad debt, in the bad stock.
The most important thing is the net cash that
you can take out of the business as the net
dividend after tax in your pocket.
That's all that counts.
That's game right there.
Yeah.
If you were stuck in that cycle of
poverty, what advice would you give to them?
If you want to escape the cycle of poverty,
be friends with at least one rich person because
all the rich people want to
teach you how they become rich.
They want to give you, they want to help
you, they want to mentor you, they want to give
you some money to start your business.
The poor will only bring you down.
And remember, don't always try to make
people like you because when you're successful, you
will have haters.
If you're prepared to say, let them, whatever they
say, then you will be ready to be very
rich.
My parents are from Thailand, but I live in Monaco.
How important is it for
an entrepreneur to leave their hometown?
It is the best thing to travel the world,
pack your bag, get your visa, get your banking
done.
All your neurons are going to change.
Every time you cross the ocean, every time
you leave your hometown, it's no longer comfortable.
You become enlightened in business, enlightened in yourself.
So it's safe to say that you
can't become a billionaire working from home.
You're not a tree.
I love that.
Hey, if you're going to sit on the
couch, go sit on the couch in Paris.
What is the deepest life quote that you've ever heard?
Things happen for you, not for me.
Yeah.
It means that things happen to you.
What does that mean to you?
It means that things happen to
build you, prepare you, to grow you.
So once you know that everything happened
for you, then you take it with courage.
You take it with a big smile and you
look for the best thing that comes as a blessing
in disguise.
The moment you look for the
good thing, the good thing appears.
You have amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yes, of course.
I give it to you.
Call me anytime.
Guys, we just interviewed another
billionaire out here in Beverly Hills.
We walked up to her and asked her,
how old were you when you become a millionaire?
She said 28, but she wondered why I
didn't ask her when she became a billionaire.
And it turns out that she owns
like 10 businesses all around the world.
She gave some incredible life advice, especially
to those that might be broke right now.
She said, what keeps poor people poor is
they don't attach themselves to the right people.
She said, find one rich person, make them
your mentor and learn everything you can from
them and watch how your life changes.
Great interview out here in Beverly Hills.
We got to keep this thing rolling
and go get this next one right now.
You guys come on.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Hi.
How did you get rich?
I know you.
I created one of the
greatest fitness products on the planet.
I know you.
You're a business owner.
More than a business owner.
I also master the art of communication.
I've sold over two and a
half billion dollars worth of products.
Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute.
I go all over the world to
be a billionaire to help the younger generation.
We're going to an event.
For one minute.
Is that okay?
It'll be worth it.
I've interviewed 40 billionaires in the last four years.
Can I get one minute with you?
Yes, you can.
Is that okay?
That's a good pitch, by the way.
See?
It works.
Did you come from a lot of money?
Absolutely not.
Flat-ass broke.
I'm going to tell you something.
I also raised a little boy from South Central.
He's also the host of a
documentary called How We're Going Home.
We're gonna do a ...
The best thing in life, you can do
is go down and spring right back up.
And that's exactly what you did.
Oh, I've done it more than once.
Life happens for you, not to you.
Were you good at sales?
I'm one of the best
it's ever been on the planet.
That's what I do.
You know what pitching is?
Yeah.
Getting someone to say yes, because if you can
get one yes, you can get a credit card.
That's Gabe right there.
I realized at a very early age, if
you can communicate what you want, you can persuade
someone else to say yes to you, you win.
Your parents were broke.
If you could go back in time and give
your parents one piece of advice, what would that
be?
and thank you for asking that.
Guys, we have to stop filming
to protect the privacy of our guests.
I like getting kicked out of places.
Yeah.
No, because I'll tell you why.
Don't ask for permission.
Ask for forgiveness.
Something nobody knows.
I don't know if I should tell you this.
I was an actress early on in my career,
and I couldn't find an agent.
I was chased around a lot of desks.
There was no Me Too movement.
There was no protection for people like me.
There was the casting couch.
And so I created my own manager.
I literally figured out how actors get hired,
and I created a woman called Lindsay Maxwell
and a company called Creative Management, CMA.
And for three years, I represented myself.
I got my own gigs.
So don't wait.
And I didn't ask anybody for permission
because sometimes the rules don't work for you.
And is that okay?
I don't know.
Break them and find out.
So what's your name?
What's my name?
My name is Dr. Forbes Riley.
Forbes is in the magazines.
Did you have people that doubted you in business?
Everybody doubted me.
Nobody thought I was going to be successful.
In fact, I was made fun of on television.
There was a TV series called Pitch Men.
They literally said my product would never work.
I've sold a million dollars a day on home shopping.
2.5 million of something that they said wouldn't work.
How do you know?
You're not supposed to ask
a woman how old she is.
How do you know?
Oh my goodness.
All right, I'm turning 66 and I'm just getting started.
I would have guessed 35 maybe.
Oh, see now that's a...
Oh, yeah, you are a charmer.
You're an innate pitcher.
I got to tell you, I very rarely met somebody
who can pitch as well as I did.
I think you may be that guy.
If me and you died tomorrow
and you had one more message to leave
with the younger generation, what would that be?
You know, I don't know if
you get to live more than once,
but if you live right
the first time, once is enough.
I love that.
You have amazing advice.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Absolutely.
Guys, we just interviewed
our second billion dollar entrepreneur in this video alone,
but I want you all to notice something.
Look, both of them.
Matter of fact, all of the billionaires
that I've interviewed all mastered one skill.
They mastered attention.
That is the most valuable skill
you can master in today's world.
Now, before we go get our next interview,
I've got a crazy announcement to make for you.
On February 23rd,
I'm hosting the first ever Viral Content Summit.
This is a live one day virtual event
where I'm breaking down step-by-step
how I've generated billions of views,
gained over 20 million views,
20 million followers on social media,
and turned content into a multi-million dollar business.
I'm gonna be teaching how to grow on social media,
how to monetize,
and how to turn attention into real leverage.
But I'm not doing this alone.
I'm gonna be bringing in
some of the biggest content creators in the world
that you know,
people with millions of followers and subscribers,
people that have generated
hundreds of millions of views on social media.
They're gonna be teaching you how they did it.
But here's the crazy part, guys.
It is 100% free to get access to,
but there's just one catch.
This is a live event.
It only happens once.
There are no replays,
and there will be no recordings.
So look, if you're serious
about building a brand in 2026,
this is not optional.
Now, here's where this gets even better, though.
When you grab your spot inside our school community
for the summit, which you'll see in the description,
you'll also unlock the School of Mentors.
That means every single week,
you get direct access to the millionaires
and the billionaires that you see me interview
on this channel.
You're asking your questions directly to them,
and they're mentoring you directly live
on these calls that I host.
And like I said, look, if you join now,
before the event on Friday,
February 23rd,
you can join 100% for free,
but you do not have a lot of time.
So look, go down right now,
click the link in the description of this video
to get access to the Viral Content Summit
and the number one most powerful entrepreneur community
and network in the entire world.
So I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I have a question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
You're Miles Garrett, right?
Nice to meet you, man.
Can I get one minute with you real quick?
So how did you get rich
for the people that don't know?
I played defensive.
I've been for the Cleveland Browns.
You're one of the greatest defensive ends of all time.
I mean, if you say so.
Tell the people what records you broke this year.
For those that don't know, man.
Single season sack record.
The most of anybody in a single season.
Yes, sir.
What was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
I can't say that.
More than 10 million?
Yes.
More than 15 million?
More than 20 million?
Yes.
More than $20 million, man.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No.
Was that one of your driving factors?
Was that motivation for you?
Absolutely.
I wanted to give my family a better life,
better lifestyle, especially my gran.
She has always been my driving factor,
and she passed right before I got into college,
and I always write her name down on my tape.
When a lot of athletes go into money,
they're not used to seeing that much money,
and a lot of them go and blow it.
What are you doing to preserve your wealth for years,
for decades, to come to build that generational wealth?
Teams and energy.
Renewable energy.
You said energy?
Yes, sir.
Part owner in the Cavs,
and I'm looking forward to being an owner
in a Premier League team sometime soon.
You're part of a basketball team, man.
I am.
I'm going to challenge you.
Take me back to the most life-changing conversation
you ever had.
What's the greatest piece of advice
you received throughout your career?
Probably sat down in high school,
and I was with my parents,
and my head coach at the time for football,
he was also the AD,
and they told me I needed
to be all in or all out.
You know, you can't do anything half-assed.
If I wanted to be great,
then I had to give everything to it.
I was really into basketball,
and I wanted to just do football on the side.
It was like, if you're going to do it,
make the most out of it,
and see what you can become,
but don't play around with it.
Did you ever worry about what people thought about you?
Never.
Why not?
I'm sure you've had haters with this amount of success.
I mean, you are who you are.
Jalen Brown told me that
they don't build statues for haters.
They build them for people
that do things like Miles Garrett.
You damn right.
How old are you?
30 years old.
Do you believe in God?
I do.
How important has faith been for your success?
All glory goes to God, everything that I do.
You know, every sack I point up to this guy,
I kiss my wrist,
and I have a cross there as well,
and I believe that's almost completely
part of my process and my success.
Jesus is king.
Every day.
You got amazing advice, my friend.
Thank you so much, man.
I got to ask you, man.
I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah.
Guys, we just interviewed one of
the greatest NFL players of all time,
Miles Garrett.
Okay, this last season,
like we talked about in the interview,
he broke the single season sack records.
More sacks in a single season than any
NFL player in the history of the league.
Great interview out here in Beverly Hills,
and what did he say, man?
He gives it all to God.
Rather all in or all out.
He went all in.
Let's go get this next interview out here, you guys.
Come on.
All right, you guys, so look.
So we are right now outside
of the Beverly Hills Hilton Hotel,
and the reason why we're here is because
we got invited to the Legend of Aviation Awards,
and apparently this show hosts more billionaires than
just about any event in the entire world,
and we got invited to do interviews here.
Now, the problem is billionaires are not going to
stop and talk to me on the red carpet
if I'm wearing a damn Hollister sweater.
So it's time to go back, put
the suit on, come back out here,
lock in, and interview some billionaires.
So let's make it happen.
All right, you guys, so as you can see,
man, we changed up the style a little bit.
I'm in the suit because, look, if I'm going to
try to interview billionaires that are all in tuxedos, man,
I got to accommodate to their style and their wardrobe.
So we're about to head in right now to
the Beverly Hills Hilton to go meet some billionaires
and some of the richest people
out here in Beverly Hills, you guys.
Come on.
All right, you guys, look.
So right behind me is Ken Richie.
Okay, he is the private jet billionaire.
I think he's like the CEO or founder of Flexjet.
Okay, the guy became a multi-billionaire.
So we're going to try and hold a portion
and see if he'll do an interview with us.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes, hi.
A question for you.
I started a channel at the University
of Texas when I was 20 years old,
grew it to 20 million followers, and I've
interviewed 39 billionaires in the last four years,
like Mark Cuban, Michael Rubin, Tom Cruise.
Can I get just one minute with you real quick?
Of course, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who am I here with today?
Ken Richie.
And what is your company?
Flexjet.
We do fractional ownership of about
370 planes and about 5,000 employees worldwide.
How old were you when you became a billionaire?
About seven, eight years ago.
Seven, eight years ago.
Yeah, I mean, you know, it's kind of a nebula.
It's not like a line in
the, they're not a line of demarcation.
Among yourself and the most
highly successful people you know,
your network of billionaire friends, what
do they all have in common?
Passion.
Passion for sure.
But I would also say many of
my very successful friends are fanatical about detail.
Fanatical attention to detail, right?
Just paying attention, knowing the little
things that make a big move.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
Was there a moment early on
in your life that told you,
I wanted to kind of go
out there and create an empire?
You know when you're rich?
When?
When you have 25 times your annual spend.
So if you live on $1,000 a year,
you're rich at $25,000.
People say, well, I want
$10 million, I want $12 million.
That's the wrong idea.
The right idea is how much does it take
for you to live the life you want to live?
And some people, it's $100,000.
Some people, it's $10 million.
Well, if it takes you
$10 million to enjoy your lifestyle,
then you need $250 million.
So it's more of a function of how you
live and not a function of what you have.
You have a very interesting philosophy on wealth
in terms of your being
open about it with your family,
which is maybe controversial to some people.
Can you explain that philosophy for my viewers?
Well, sure.
I mean, number one is that I
often say when kids are growing up,
we've been taught to talk about sex and not money.
But the analogy is, the answer
is money is much more important.
Making sure your kids know how
to be stewards of what they have.
And the other thing is,
if you talk about trust, right?
You talk about good advice.
One of the most interesting pieces of
advice I got was from President Clinton.
I was his pilot for a year and
a half when he was running for president.
And he used to start a conversation.
He would say something like,
I don't know you very well,
but you know, I sleep way too long.
And he would say to me,
if you hate someone, if you start
a conversation by displaying one of your faults,
you're telling people you trust them.
So if I tell you, I
ate too many French fries, right?
I didn't have to tell you that.
But you say, Ken trusted me
and he mentioned that to me.
So now when you go to your kids
and you want to create trust with them,
you have to tell them secrets.
You have to open up yourself.
If you're going to create trust with your children,
they have to know the secrets.
So financial is one of the huge secrets.
How old are you now?
I'm 69.
My last question.
You're 69?
Oh, stop.
My last question for you, Ken.
If you and you died tomorrow and you had
one more message to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
The key to success is empathy.
Think about others.
Think about your employees.
Think about your family.
Get up every day being empathetic
and sympathetic for those around you.
People remember how you make them feel.
Exactly.
They don't remember your name,
but they remember how they felt.
Thank you so much for your time.
It's a pleasure.
Thank you for what you're doing.
Very well needed.
And you're doing a great job.
I connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Absolutely.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video, man.
The Beverly Hills billionaires just went crazy.
But I need you to stop right now.
Like, subscribe for amazing content.
Coming to the School of Hard Knocks every week.
Because nobody else is bringing you the expert
insights from the richest people and all the
billionaires on the planet.
And go down and click the
link in the description of this video.
Because you can get access to the
number one most powerful entrepreneur community and network
in the world.
Where every week I host live events,
live calls with the billionaires and the millionaires
I interview on this channel.
So I can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.